Guide to the Glenway Wescott Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1900-89, n.d.; Series I; 53.76; (129 boxes)
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE
    - Brenan, Gerald, 1951-52 (Box 39, Folder 523)
    - Brennan, Thomas, 1945 Mar 2 (Box 39, Folder 524)
    - Brent, Harvey, 1955 Sep 12 (Box 39, Folder 525)
    - Breuer, Bessie, 1959 Feb 14, n.d. (Box 39, Folder 526)
    - Brewer, Joseph
      Related Archival Materials note
      See: Katherine Anne Porter, Box 91, folders 1364-1365
    - Brinnin, John Malcolm, 1936 May 25 (Box 39, Folder 527)
    - Britton, Coburn, 1970-75 (Box 39, Folder 528)
    - Brodkey, Harold, 1959, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 529)
    - Bromfield, Louis, [1927] (Box 39, Folder 530)
      to Eugene Saxton [copy to GW]
    - Brooks, Gladys, 1961-72, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 531)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1947-62 (Box 40, Folder 532)
    - GW to Brooks, Van Wyck and Brooks, Gladys, 1949 Dec 23 (Box 40, Folder 533)
    - Brown, Grace Lusk, 1927, 1929 (Box 40, Folder 534)
    - Brown, John Mason, Mr. & Mrs., 1959, 1967, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 535)
    - Bruccoli, Matthew J., 1964-78 (Box 40, Folder 536)
    - Bruder, Harold, 1962-83, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 537-538)
    - Buckingham, Robert, 1951-72 (Box 40, Folder 539)
    - Buechner, Frederick, 1978 Dec 10 (Box 40, Folder 540)
    - Bull, Wesson, 1923, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 541)
    - Burden, William, A. M., 1944-65 (Box 40, Folder 542)
    - Burke, Kenneth, 1927-62 (Box 40, Folder 543)
    - Burns, John Horne, 1949 Jan 30 (Box 40, Folder 544)
    - Butcher, Fanny, 1927 Sep 17 (Box 40, Folder 545)
      Contains only letter from GW
      to Butcher
    - Butler, Earl, 1961-1975 Nov (Box 40, Folder 546-548)
      to GW; includes letters from GW & MW
    - Butler, Earl, 1975 Dec-1984, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 549-550)
    - GW to Butler, Earl, 1964-78, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 551)
    - Butts, Anthony, 1920-28, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 552)
    - Butts, Mary, 1923-27, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 553)
    - Byington, Robert, 1964-73 (Box 41, Folder 554)
    - Bynner, Witter, 1938-61 (Box 41, Folder 555)
      to MW & GW; includes letter from GW
    - Byrne, Evelyn B., 1963-72 (Box 41, Folder 556)
    - "B" general, 1933-84, n.d. (Box 41, Folder 557-560)
    - "B" general, 1933-84, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 561-562)
    - Cabell, James Branch, 1940 Nov 7 (Box 42, Folder 563)
    - Cabell, Ury, 1939, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 564)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1937-88, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 565-566)
    - Caetani, Marguerite, 1952 Dec 13 (Box 42, Folder 567)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1939-84 (Box 42, Folder 568)
      to MW & Barbara and Lloyd Wescott
    - Caldwell, Erskine, 1962-83 (Box 42, Folder 569)
    - Cameron, Gledhill, 1976-80 (Box 42, Folder 570)
    - Cameron, Rory, 1949-72 (Box 42, Folder 571)
    - Campbell, Joseph, 1943-72 (Box 42, Folder 572)
    - Campbell, Sandy, 1950-81 (Box 42, Folder 573)
    - Canfield, Cass; Canfield, Jane, 1964-76, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 574)
    - Capote, Truman, 1962-83 (Box 42, Folder 575)
    - Cárdenas, Héctor, 1970-74 (Box 43, Folder 576)
      to GW & Ivan Van Auw Jr.
      includes letters from GW
    - Carnevali, Emanuel, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 577)
    - Carnochan, Bliss; Carnochan, Brigitte, 1981-85 (Box 43, Folder 578)
    - Carrieri, Raffaele, 1949-51 (Box 43, Folder 579)
    - Carroll, Jon, 1964-73 (Box 43, Folder 580)
    - Carson, Rachel, 1951 (Box 43, Folder 581)
      to Carson
    - Cartier-Bresson, Henri, 1947-87, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 582)
    - Cartwright, Curt; Cartwright, Connie, 1987-88, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 583)
    - [Carver, Rosemary?], 1959 Dec 31, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 584)
      to GW, Barbara Wescott, & George
    - Cary, Joyce, 1951-53 (Box 43, Folder 585)
    - Cassou, Jean, 1948 Dec 27 (Box 43, Folder 586)
    - Celle, Henri de la, 1949-76 (Box 43, Folder 587)
    - Chambers, Robert, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 588)
    - Chandlee, William H., 1951-87, n.d. (Box 43, Folder 589-595)
    - GW to Chandlee, William H., 1952-78, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 596-603)
    - Charlton, James, 1951-55 (Box 44, Folder 604)
    - Charlton, George; Charlton, Margaret, 1986-87 (Box 44, Folder 605)
    - Cheever, John, 1957-76, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 606)
    - Chesser, Mary, 1953-83, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 607)
    - GW to Chesser, Mary, 1968-75, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 608)
    - Chiappinelli, Don, 1979-82, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 609)
    - Chipps, [Isobel?], Lady, 1949 Jun 27 (Box 45, Folder 610)
    - Christenson, C. L., 1963, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 611)
    - Christenson, Cornelia, 1961-78, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 612)
    - Christopher, Robert, 1952, 1954, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 613)
    - Christopher, William, 1964-73, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 614)
    - Chute, Marchette, 1950-81 (Box 45, Folder 615)
    - City College of the City University of New York, 1964-66 (Box 45, Folder 616)
    - Clark, Eleanor, 1942-76, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 617)
    - Clark, Kenneth, Sir; Clark, Jane, Lady, 1947-76, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 618)
      to MW & GW; includes letters from GW
    - Clarke, Gilmore, 1971-80 (Box 45, Folder 619)
    - Cockrell, Bill
      See: Mike Lifrieri, Box 66, folder 967
    - Cocteau, Jean, 1925-64, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 620)
      to MW, GW, & Emile Darlion
      includes letter from GW to MW
      re Cocteau
    - Coghill, Nevill, 1954 Jun 14 (Box 45, Folder 621)
    - Cole, Marion, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 622)
    - Colby, Charles, 1950 Feb 4 (Box 45, Folder 623)
    - Colcord, Lincoln, 1927 Jul 28 (Box 45, Folder 624)
    - Collard, C.B., 1945-63 (Box 45, Folder 625)
    - Colum, Mary; Colum, Padraic, 1944-64, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 626)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1964-65 (Box 45, Folder 627)
    - Connolly, Cyril, 1943-73, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 628)
    - Connolly, John, 1952-84, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 629-631)
    - Connolly, William, 1965-77 (Box 46, Folder 632)
    - Cook, Katharine, 1959-60, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 633)
    - Cook, Mariana, 1983 May 24 (Box 46, Folder 634)
    - Coons, Rudolph, 1933-48 (Box 46, Folder 635)
    - Copland, Aaron, 1939(?)-71, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 636)
    - Corder, Donald L., 1957-69, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 637)
    - Cornell, Joseph, 1956-64 (Box 46, Folder 638)
    - Cota, Robert, 1975 Aug 27 (Box 46, Folder 639)
    - Cottenet, R. L., 1931-40, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 640)
    - Coward-McCann, Inc., 1965 (Box 46, Folder 641)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1951-73 (Box 46, Folder 642)
    - Craig, Edward Gordon, 1932 (Box 46, Folder 643)
    - Crane, Josephine, 1937.66, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 644)
    - Crosby, Caresse, 1954 Feb 10 (Box 47, Folder 645)
    - Crosthwaite, Moore, 1932-88, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 646-649)
    - Cummings, E.E., 1951 Feb 21 (Box 47, Folder 650)
    - Cunard, Maud [Emerald]; Cunard, Nancy, 1940-65, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 651)
    - Cunninghame-Graham, R. B., 1921-25 (Box 47, Folder 652)
    - Curie, Eve, 1943 (Box 47, Folder 653)
    - Curtis Brown, Ltd., 1929 Feb 28 (Box 47, Folder 654)
    - Curtiss, Mina, 1941-77, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 655)
      to MW & GW; includes letters from
      GW, Edward James, and The Viking
      Press to MC
    - Curtius, Ernst Robert, 1931-48, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 656)
    - "C" general, 1921-87, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 657)
    - "C" general, 1921-87, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 658-659)
    - Dahl-Wolfe, Louise, 1976 Jul 19 (Box 48, Folder 660)
    - Dane, Elsa Maria; Dane, Evaluaria, 1945-60 (Box 48, Folder 661)
    - Danziger, Else; Danziger, Louis, 1926-60 (Box 48, Folder 662)
    - Davis, Christopher, 1960-69 (Box 48, Folder 663)
    - de Menocal, Richard, 1950-63, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 664)
    - Deane, Peter, 1962-65, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 665)
    - Delacorte Press, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 666)
    - Derleth, August, 1936 Jul 2 (Box 48, Folder 667)
    - Deutsch, Babette, 1958-78 (Box 48, Folder 668)
    - d'Harnoncourt, Réné, 1953-77 (Box 48, Folder 669)
      to MW; includes letters from GW
    - De Vries, Peter, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 670)
    - The Dial Press, 1946-53 (Box 48, Folder 671)
    - Diamond, Dan, 1980-84, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 672)
    - Diamond, David, 1940-83, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 673)
    - Dinesen, Isak [Karen Blixen], 1958-60, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 674)
    - Dobbs, John, 1936-62 (Box 48, Folder 675)
    - Donneley, Lucy Martin, 1939-45 (Box 48, Folder 676)
    - Donohoe, Eileen, 1959-62, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 677)
    - Dos Passos, John, 1941-42, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 678)
    - Doubleday, Nelson, 1944 Mar 30 (Box 48, Folder 679)
    - Doubleday & Co., Inc., 1947-75, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 680)
    - Draper, Ruth, 1927-56, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 681)
    - Dudley, Katherine, 1950-61, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 682)
    - Dunn, Joseph M., 1978-81, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 683)
    - Dunoyer de Segonzac, André, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 684)
    - Dupee, Fred W., 1945-64 (Box 49, Folder 685)
    - "D" general, 1927-86, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 686-687)
    - Eakins Press, 1976-78 (Box 49, Folder 688)
    - Eastman, Max, 1947 Feb 9 (Box 49, Folder 689)
    - Eberhart, Richard, 1951 Aug 26 (Box 49, Folder 690)
    - Edel, Leon, 1967-80 (Box 49, Folder 691)
    - Edwards, Agustin, Mrs. (Malu), 1974-88, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 692)
    - Einstein, Albert, 1942 Sep 11 (Box 49, Folder 693)
    - Eliot, T. S., 1921-50, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 694)
      to GW & MW; includes letter from MW
    - Ellenzweig, Allen, 1981-82 (Box 49, Folder 695)
    - Ellison, Ralph, 1969 Mar 8 (Box 49, Folder 696)
      Contains only letter from GW to Ellison
    - Ellman, Richard, 1962 Jan 6 (Box 49, Folder 697)
    - Esquire, 1957-63 (Box 49, Folder 698)
    - Etting, Elmen, 1963-64 (Box 49, Folder 699)
    - Evans, Abbie Huston, 1963-66, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 700)
    - Evans, Helen Parker, 1919-74, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 701)
    - Evans, Walker, 1961 Dec 10 (Box 50, Folder 702)
    - "E" general, 1936-88, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 703)
    - Fadiman, Clifton, 1947, 1962 (Box 50, Folder 704)
    - Falk, Andrew, 1980-87 (Box 50, Folder 705)
    - Falké, Pierre, 1930-31 (Box 50, Folder 706)
    - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, Inc., 1951-88, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 707)
    - Farrell, James, 1947 Feb 20 (Box 50, Folder 708)
    - Faÿ, Bernard, 1925-32 (Box 50, Folder 709)
    - Felderhof, Anna; Felderhof, Hendrik, 1945-46 (Box 50, Folder 710)
    - Ferber, Edna, 1945-60 (Box 50, Folder 711)
    - Ferreira, [Francisio?], 1942 (Box 50, Folder 712)
    - Fillini, Mel, 1953-57, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 713)
    - Fingerhood, Patricia [Danielson?], 1974-86 (Box 50, Folder 714)
    - Fischman, Iver, 1963-64 (Box 50, Folder 715)
    - Fitch, Noel, 1977-83 (Box 50, Folder 716)
    - Fitzgerald, F. Scott, 1934 Feb (Box 50, Folder 717)
    - Flanner, Janet, 1940-87, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 718)
    - Fleet, Henry, 1944 (Box 50, Folder 719)
    - Fleet, Simon, 1947-55 (Box 50, Folder 720)
    - Flores, Bill, 1952-55, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 721)
    - Fontan, Jack, 1952-72, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 722)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1957-87, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 723)
    - Ford, Ford Madox, 1921-31, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 724)
    - Ford, Hugh, 1964-88, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 725)
      to GW, MW, Leah Sloshberg,
      & Peter Brown; includes
      letter from GW
    - Ford, Ruth, 1964-83, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 726)
    - Ford, Thomas I., 1966 (Box 51, Folder 727)
      Contains only letters from MW
    - Forster, E. M., 1941-64, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 728)
      to MW & GW; includes letters from MW & GW
    - Foster, Harvey, 1933-34, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 729)
    - Fouts, Denham, 1939 Aug 14 (Box 51, Folder 730)
    - Frankenberg, Lloyd
      See: Loren MacIver, Box 74, folder 1080
    - Franks, Dobbs, 1959-60 (Box 51, Folder 731)
    - Frash, Robert M., 1947-88, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 732)
    - Freer, Agnes Lee, 1925-30 (Box 51, Folder 733)
    - French, Jared; French, Margaret, 1938-66, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 734)
    - Fritz, Chester, 1929, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 735)
      to GW & MW; includes letters from GW & MW
    - Fuller, Henry B., 1923-27 (Box 52, Folder 736)
    - Furmas, J.C., 1963-84 (Box 52, Folder 737)
    - "F" general, 1934-87, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 738)
    - Gado, Frank, 1965-83, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 739)
    - Gagnon, John, 1957-67, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 740)
    - Galantière, Lewis, 1965 Oct 10 (Box 52, Folder 741)
    - Gale, Zona, 1927 Aug (Box 52, Folder 742)
      to GW & "Mr. Wells"
    - Gallery of Modern Art, 1964-65 (Box 52, Folder 743)
    - Gamwell, James, 1958-78, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 744)
    - Gardner, Isabella, 1966 Oct 14 (Box 52, Folder 745)
    - Garrett, Julian, 1953-73 (Box 52, Folder 746)
    - Garrett, George, 1962-63 (Box 52, Folder 747)
    - Gathorne-Hardy, Robert, 1939-41 (Box 52, Folder 748)
    - Gebhard, Paul, 1956-87, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 749-750)
      See also: Institute for Sex Research, Box 59, folder 851
    - Gebhardt, W. Reading, 1959-72 (Box 53, Folder 751)
      to GW, Lloyd & Barbara Wescott
    - George Braziller, Inc., 1962-66 (Box 53, Folder 752)
    - Gill, Cecil Hope, 1966-84, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 753)
    - Gillum, Jack Lawson, 1952 (Box 53, Folder 754)
    - Girling, H. K., 1961-62 (Box 53, Folder 755)
    - Goldbeck, Eva, 1920-31 (Box 53, Folder 756)
      to MW & GW; includes letter
      from EG to "Betty"
    - Goldstone, Richard, 1961-75 (Box 53, Folder 757)
      to GW; includes letter from
      GW to Thornton Wilder
    - Golik, Edwin, 1953-67 (Box 53, Folder 758)
      to GW; includes letter from EG
      to Evan Thomas
    - Goodwin, Philip, 1942-58 (Box 53, Folder 759)
    - Gordon, Ruth, 1950 Mar 9 (Box 53, Folder 760)
    - Gotham Book Mart and Gallery, 1972-85, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 761)
    - Gowing, Lawrence, 1965-70, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 762)
      to MW; includes letter from GW
    - Goyen, William, 1950-74, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 763)
    - Graff, Robert; Graff, Marjorie, 1977-83, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 764)
    - Graham-Lujan, James, 1943-66, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 765)
    - Grand Street, 1981 (Box 53, Folder 766)
      Contains only letter from
      Grand Street to Rodger Strauss
    - Granville-Barker, Helen, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 767)
    - Green, Gretchen, 1962-70, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 768)
    - Green, James Wilder, 1951, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 769)
    - Green, Julien, 1928-71, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 770)
    - Greene, Graham, 1929-62 (Box 53, Folder 771)
      to GW; includes letter from GW,
    - Gregory, Alyse, 1940-61, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 772)
    - Grog, Andy, 1957 (Box 53, Folder 773)
    - Grolier Club, 1960, 1975, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 774)
    - Grow, Lawrence, 1967-71 (Box 53, Folder 775)
    - Guérin, Jacques, 1928-87, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 776-780)
    - GW to Guérin, Jacques, 1931-75, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 781)
    - Gunther, John, 1962, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 782)
    - Gyldendalske boghandel, 1960-62 (Box 54, Folder 783)
    - "G" general, 1921-87, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 784-785)
    - H.B. Playwrights Foundation, Inc., 1964-66 (Box 55, Folder 786)
    - H. D., 1921 (Box 55, Folder 787)
    - Haeni, Susan, 1980 (Box 55, Folder 788)
    - Hall, Lillian, 1969-78, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 789)
    - Hallacy, David, 1963-85 (Box 55, Folder 790)
    - Halliday, Richard, 1931-38, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 791)
    - Hamish Hamilton, Ltd., 1944-63, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 792)
    - Hammond, Anne, 1957-77, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 793)
    - Hammond, May, 1954-68, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 794)
    - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, 1967-79 (Box 55, Folder 795)
    - Harold Ober Associates, 1965-89, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 796)
    - Harper, Joyce, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 797)
    - Harper & Row, Publishers, 1925-84, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 798-802)
    - Harper's Bazaar, 1940 Aug 19 (Box 56, Folder 803)
    - Harper's Magazine, 1960-64 (Box 56, Folder 804)
      See also: Harper and Row, Box 56, folders 798-802
    - Harris, Ray Baker, 1931-60 (Box 56, Folder 805)
    - Harrison, Dora, 1948-83, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 806)
    - Harrison, Francis Burton, 1930 Oct 12 (Box 56, Folder 807)
    - Harrison, Geoffrey, 1941-45, n.d. (Box 56, Folder 808)
    - Harrison, Gilbert, 1979-83 (Box 56, Folder 809)
    - Harrison, Kiko, 1946 Apr 25 (Box 56, Folder 810)
    - Harrison, Peter, 1964-65 (Box 56, Folder 811)
    - Hartley, Marsden, 1937-42 (Box 56, Folder 812)
    - Hatfield, Ann; Hatfield, Ted, 1927-88 (Box 57, Folder 813)
    - Haverford College, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 814)
    - Hecht, Anthony, 1979 Jan 11 (Box 57, Folder 815)
    - Heckscher, August, 1962-87 (Box 57, Folder 816)
    - Heilbrun, Carolyn, 1975 Jun 21 (Box 57, Folder 817)
    - Hellman, Lillian, 1949-75 (Box 57, Folder 818)
    - Hergesheimer, Joseph, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 819)
    - Herr, Ryman, 1957-76 (Box 57, Folder 820)
      to Herr, Lehigh Railroad
      Company, and Dr. Raymond Fidellow
      also includes letter from
      Tharrington, Smith & Hargrove
      re. Thaine Clark
    - Herring, Robert
      See: Life and Letters Today, Box 66, folder 966
    - Hersey, John, 1947-68 (Box 57, Folder 821)
    - Highsmith, Patricia, 1965 May 4 (Box 57, Folder 822)
    - Hirschbeck, Loretta, 1961-62 (Box 57, Folder 823)
    - Hirth, Fred, 1960-81, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 824)
    - Hitrec, J. G., 1948-50 (Box 57, Folder 825)
    - Hobgood, George, 1943-78, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 826)
    - Hobson, Joseph W., 1974-77, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 827)
    - Hobson, Laura Z., 1949-65 (Box 57, Folder 828)
    - Hobson, Verna; Hobson, Wilder, 1964-67, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 829)
    - Hofer, Philip, 1936-78, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 830)
    - Holliday Bookshop, 1950 Nov (Box 57, Folder 831)
    - Hollins College, 1967-69 (Box 57, Folder 832)
    - Holzhauer, Robin, 1945-46 (Box 57, Folder 833)
    - Horgan, Paul, 1962-76, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 834)
    - [Howard], Chuck, 1949-65, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 835)
    - Howard, Richard, 1966-70, n.d. (Box 57, Folder 836)
    - Hughes, Richard, 1969, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 837)
    - Hugo, Jean, 1971 Aug (Box 58, Folder 838)
    - Hull, Helen, 1951-62 (Box 58, Folder 839)
    - Humphrey, Paul H., 1918-19 (Box 58, Folder 840)
    - Humphrey, William, 1951-66 (Box 58, Folder 841)
    - Hunter College, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 842)
    - Hunterdon County, New Jersey agencies, 1964-80 (Box 58, Folder 843)
    - Huppler, Dudley, 1950-70, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 844)
    - Hurd, Clement, 1935-70, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 845)
    - Huxley, Aldous, 1949 Dec 3 (Box 58, Folder 846)
    - "H" general, 1928-87, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 847-849)
    - Inge, William, 1950-75, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 850)
      & letter from WI to [Russell?] Lynes
    - Institute for Sex Research, Indiana University, 1956-76 (Box 59, Folder 851)
      See also: Paul Gebhard, Box 52, folders 749-750
      See also: Alfred Kinsey, Box 61, folder 885
    - Isherwood, Christopher, 1939-79, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 852)
    - Ivry, Benjamin, 1981-82, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 853)
    - "I" general, 1956-80, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 854)
    - Jackson, Charles, 1944-47, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 855)
    - Jackson, David, 1953-56 (Box 59, Folder 856)
    - Jacob, Max, 1931-33 (Box 59, Folder 857)
    - James, Edward to MW, 1941-71, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 858)
    - James, Elizabeth, 1963-80, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 859)
    - Janta, Alexander, 1944-68 (Box 59, Folder 860)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1934-79, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 861)
    - Johnson, Essie, 1925-76, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 862)
    - Johnson, Philip, 1965-87, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 863)
    - Johnson, Samuel F., 1943-76, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 864)
    - Josephson, Hannah, 1958-73 (Box 60, Folder 865)
    - "J" general, 1930-87, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 866)
    - Kahn, Sy, 1954-65, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 867)
    - Karen Horney Clinic, 1959-74, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 868)
    - Karp, Irwin, 1964-65 (Box 60, Folder 869)
    - Karsh, Yousef, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 870)
    - Kauffer, E. McKnight, 1941-51 (Box 60, Folder 871)
    - Kauffman, Herbert H., 1945-51, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 872)
    - Kaufman, George S.; Kaufman, Beatrice, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 873)
    - Kazin, Alfred, 1949 Feb 21 (Box 60, Folder 874)
    - Keck, Frances, 1962, 1987, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 875)
    - Keenan, Brendan, 1946 Oct 19, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 876)
    - Kelleher, Marion, 1974-80, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 877)
      to MW, GW, & Lloyd Wescott
    - Kelly, Leon, 1946-74 (Box 61, Folder 878)
    - Kendall, George, 1967-76 (Box 61, Folder 879)
    - Kennan, George F., 1964-76 (Box 61, Folder 880)
    - Kent, H. W., 1938-42, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 881)
    - Kepes, Gyorgy, 1945(?) Aug 6 (Box 61, Folder 882)
    - Kerr, Archibald Clark, 1945 May 8 (Box 61, Folder 883)
    - Keynes, Geoffrey, 1951-53 (Box 61, Folder 884)
      to MW; includes letters from MW
    - Kinsey, Alfred; Kinsey, Clara, 1949-62, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 885)
      to GW & MW; includes letters
      from GW, letter from AK to
      Julien Green, letter from
      AK to George Platt-Lynes
      includes inventory of GPL's
      nudes
    - Kirstein, Lincoln, 1934-87, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 886)
      to GW, MW & "George"
    - Klump, William, 1958-59, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 887)
    - Knollys, Eardley, 1925-84, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 888)
    - Knopf, Alfred A.; Knopf, Blanche, 1951-65 (Box 61, Folder 889)
    - Knowles, John, 1959-70 (Box 62, Folder 890)
    - Kochnitzky, Léon, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 891)
    - Kolbe, Frank, 1946-82 (Box 62, Folder 892)
    - Kraft, James, 1972-79 (Box 62, Folder 893)
    - Kreider, Noble, 1919-20 (Box 62, Folder 894)
    - Krementz, Jill, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 895)
    - Kronenberger, Louis, 1951 Mar 10 (Box 62, Folder 896)
    - Kuelthau, Earl, 1961-67 (Box 62, Folder 897)
    - "K" general, 1936-88, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 898-899)
    - Lacretelle, Jacques de, 1945 (Box 62, Folder 900)
    - Lago, Mary, 1979-82 (Box 62, Folder 901)
    - Lal, P., 1967 May 15 (Box 62, Folder 902)
    - Lane, Nelson Herbert, 1957, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 903)
    - Lansdale, Nelson to GW, 1939-64, n.d. (Box 62, Folder 904-911)
    - GW to Lansdale, Nelson, 1927-1941 Oct (Box 63, Folder 912-921)
    - GW to Lansdale, Nelson, 1941 Nov-1957, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 922-930)
    - MW to Lansdale, Nelson, 1940 Nov 30 (Box 64, Folder 931)
    - Lansdale, Ruth, 1964-67 (Box 64, Folder 932)
    - Larsson, Raymond Ellsworth, 1934 Feb 28 (Box 64, Folder 933)
    - Latham, Louise, 1965, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 934)
      to GW & "Earl"
    - Laughlin, James, 1939-80 (Box 64, Folder 935)
    - Lavine, Mary, 1971 Jul 30 (Box 64, Folder 936)
    - Lawrence, Jeffrey, 1974-76, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 937)
    - Lawrence, Neil ("Buddie"), 1954-56, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 938)
    - Lawrence, Seymour, 1967-72 (Box 64, Folder 939)
    - Leavitt, David, 1949-51, n.d. (Box 64, Folder 940)
      to MW; includes letters from MW,
      letter from Shin-ichi Yuize to DL,
      letter from Shin-ichi Yuize to MW
    - Leavitt, David, 1952-87, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 941-942)
    - Lebeck, Michael, 1966-80, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 943)
    - Lederer, Gertrude, 1954-79 (Box 65, Folder 944)
    - Ledoux, Louis V., 1937-38 (Box 65, Folder 945)
    - Lee, Arthur; Lee, Freddie, 1925-38, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 946)
    - Lee, Douglas, 1973-78, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 947)
    - Leffert, Henry, 1954-65 (Box 65, Folder 948)
    - Leonard, ---, 1971 (Box 65, Folder 949)
      to L
    - Lepoutre, Raymond, 1952-53, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 950-953)
    - Lepoutre, Raymond, n.d. [ca. 1952] (Box 66, Folder 954)
      [compilation of letters]
    - GW to Lepoutre, Raymond, 1952 (Box 66, Folder 955-958)
      [Contains non-correspondence notes by
      GW]
    - Lerman, Leo, 1959, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 959)
    - Lesemann, Maurice; Lesemann, Marjorie, 1918-80, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 960)
    - Leser, Hedwig, 1955-65, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 961)
    - Lewis, David, 1983-88, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 962)
    - Lewis, Peggy; Lewis, Michael, 1968-78 (Box 66, Folder 963)
    - Librairie Stock, 1930-33 (Box 66, Folder 964)
    - Library of Congress, 1963-65 (Box 66, Folder 965)
    - Life and Letters Today, 1936 May 8 (Box 66, Folder 966)
    - Lifrieri, Mike; Cockrell, Bill; --, Michael, 1955-76, n.d. (Box 66, Folder 967)